{"problemsArray": [
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 5)(2x - 5)", "-(2x - 5)(-2x - 5)", "(-2x + 5)(-2x - 5)", "-(-2x + 5)(2x + 5)"], "answer": "(2x + 5)(2x - 5)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (2x)^2 - 5^2\na \u003d (2x)^2, b \u003d 5^2", "question": "Factor:\n4x^2 - 25", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(10x + 6)(10x - 6)", "-(10x - 6)(-10x - 6)", "(-10x + 6)(-10x - 6)", "-(-10x + 6)(10x + 6)"], "answer": "(10x + 6)(10x - 6)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (10x)^2 - 6^2\na \u003d (10x)^2, b \u003d 6^2", "question": "Factor:\n100x^2 - 36", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(10x + 3)(10x - 3)", "-(10x - 3)(-10x - 3)", "(-10x + 3)(-10x - 3)", "-(-10x + 3)(10x + 3)"], "answer": "(10x + 3)(10x - 3)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (10x)^2 - 3^2\na \u003d (10x)^2, b \u003d 3^2", "question": "Factor:\n100x^2 - 9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 10)(x + 10)", "-(x + 10)(-x + 10)", "(-x - 10)(-x + 10)", "-(-x - 10)(x - 10)"], "answer": "(x - 10)(x + 10)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 10^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 10^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 100", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(4x + 10)(4x - 10)", "-(4x - 10)(-4x - 10)", "(-4x + 10)(-4x - 10)", "-(-4x + 10)(4x + 10)"], "answer": "(4x + 10)(4x - 10)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (4x)^2 - 10^2\na \u003d (4x)^2, b \u003d 10^2", "question": "Factor:\n16x^2 - 100", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 9)(x + 9)", "-(x + 9)(-x + 9)", "(-x - 9)(-x + 9)", "-(-x - 9)(x - 9)"], "answer": "(x - 9)(x + 9)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 9^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 9^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 81", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 9)(x - 9)", "-(x - 9)(-x - 9)", "(-x + 9)(-x - 9)", "-(-x + 9)(x + 9)"], "answer": "(x + 9)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 9^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 9^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 81", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 4)(x + 4)", "-(x + 4)(-x + 4)", "(-x - 4)(-x + 4)", "-(-x - 4)(x - 4)"], "answer": "(x - 4)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 4^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 4^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 16", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(10x + 9)(10x - 9)", "-(10x - 9)(-10x - 9)", "(-10x + 9)(-10x - 9)", "-(-10x + 9)(10x + 9)"], "answer": "(10x + 9)(10x - 9)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (10x)^2 - 9^2\na \u003d (10x)^2, b \u003d 9^2", "question": "Factor:\n100x^2 - 81", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 5)(x^2 - 5x + 25)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is positive.\nFactor the equation using the sum of cubes formula.\n(a + b)(a^2 - ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 + 5^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 125", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x - 9)(x^2 + 9x + 81)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is negative.\nFactor the equation using the difference of cubes formula.\n(a - b)(a^2 + ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 - 9^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 729", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 1)(x - 1)", "-(x - 1)(-x - 1)", "(-x + 1)(-x - 1)", "-(-x + 1)(x + 1)"], "answer": "(x + 1)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 1^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 1^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 1", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 3)(x - 3)", "-(x - 3)(-x - 3)", "(-x + 3)(-x - 3)", "-(-x + 3)(x + 3)"], "answer": "(x + 3)(x - 3)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 3^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 3^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 9)(x - 9)", "-(x - 9)(-x - 9)", "(-x + 9)(-x - 9)", "-(-x + 9)(x + 9)"], "answer": "(x + 9)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 9^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 9^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 81", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 4)(x^2 - 4x + 16)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is positive.\nFactor the equation using the sum of cubes formula.\n(a + b)(a^2 - ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 + 4^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 64", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 3)(x^2 - 3x + 9)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is positive.\nFactor the equation using the sum of cubes formula.\n(a + b)(a^2 - ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 + 3^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 27", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x - 8)(x^2 + 8x + 64)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is negative.\nFactor the equation using the difference of cubes formula.\n(a - b)(a^2 + ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 - 8^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 512", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(7x + 3)(7x - 3)", "-(7x - 3)(-7x - 3)", "(-7x + 3)(-7x - 3)", "-(-7x + 3)(7x + 3)"], "answer": "(7x + 3)(7x - 3)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (7x)^2 - 3^2\na \u003d (7x)^2, b \u003d 3^2", "question": "Factor:\n49x^2 - 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 6)(x^2 - 6x + 36)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is positive.\nFactor the equation using the sum of cubes formula.\n(a + b)(a^2 - ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 + 6^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 216", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 1)(x - 1)", "-(x - 1)(-x - 1)", "(-x + 1)(-x - 1)", "-(-x + 1)(x + 1)"], "answer": "(x + 1)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 1^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 1^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 1", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 4)(x - 4)", "-(x - 4)(-x - 4)", "(-x + 4)(-x - 4)", "-(-x + 4)(x + 4)"], "answer": "(x + 4)(x - 4)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 4^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 4^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 16", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 2)(x + 2)", "-(x + 2)(-x + 2)", "(-x - 2)(-x + 2)", "-(-x - 2)(x - 2)"], "answer": "(x - 2)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 2^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 2^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x - 8)(x^2 + 8x + 64)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is negative.\nFactor the equation using the difference of cubes formula.\n(a - b)(a^2 + ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 - 8^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 512", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 7)(x + 7)", "-(x + 7)(-x + 7)", "(-x - 7)(-x + 7)", "-(-x - 7)(x - 7)"], "answer": "(x - 7)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 7^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 7^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 49", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x - 5)(2x + 5)", "-(2x + 5)(-2x + 5)", "(-2x - 5)(-2x + 5)", "-(-2x - 5)(2x - 5)"], "answer": "(2x - 5)(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (2x)^2 - 5^2\na \u003d (2x)^2, b \u003d 5^2", "question": "Factor:\n4x^2 - 25", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 8)(x^2 - 8x + 64)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is positive.\nFactor the equation using the sum of cubes formula.\n(a + b)(a^2 - ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 + 8^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 512", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 7)(x^2 - 7x + 49)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is positive.\nFactor the equation using the sum of cubes formula.\n(a + b)(a^2 - ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 + 7^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 343", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x - 9)(x^2 + 9x + 81)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is negative.\nFactor the equation using the difference of cubes formula.\n(a - b)(a^2 + ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 - 9^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 729", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(6x + 2)(6x - 2)", "-(6x - 2)(-6x - 2)", "(-6x + 2)(-6x - 2)", "-(-6x + 2)(6x + 2)"], "answer": "(6x + 2)(6x - 2)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (6x)^2 - 2^2\na \u003d (6x)^2, b \u003d 2^2", "question": "Factor:\n36x^2 - 4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 3)(x - 3)", "-(x - 3)(-x - 3)", "(-x + 3)(-x - 3)", "-(-x + 3)(x + 3)"], "answer": "(x + 3)(x - 3)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 3^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 3^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 5)(x - 5)", "-(x - 5)(-x - 5)", "(-x + 5)(-x - 5)", "-(-x + 5)(x + 5)"], "answer": "(x + 5)(x - 5)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 5^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 5^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 25", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 5)(x^2 - 5x + 25)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is positive.\nFactor the equation using the sum of cubes formula.\n(a + b)(a^2 - ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 + 5^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 125", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 6)(x - 6)", "-(x - 6)(-x - 6)", "(-x + 6)(-x - 6)", "-(-x + 6)(x + 6)"], "answer": "(x + 6)(x - 6)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 6^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 6^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 36", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(10x + 10)(10x - 10)", "-(10x - 10)(-10x - 10)", "(-10x + 10)(-10x - 10)", "-(-10x + 10)(10x + 10)"], "answer": "(10x + 10)(10x - 10)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (10x)^2 - 10^2\na \u003d (10x)^2, b \u003d 10^2", "question": "Factor:\n100x^2 - 100", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 1)(x + 1)", "-(x + 1)(-x + 1)", "(-x - 1)(-x + 1)", "-(-x - 1)(x - 1)"], "answer": "(x - 1)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 1^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 1^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x - 3)(x^2 + 3x + 9)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is negative.\nFactor the equation using the difference of cubes formula.\n(a - b)(a^2 + ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 - 3^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 27", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x - 7)(x^2 + 7x + 49)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is negative.\nFactor the equation using the difference of cubes formula.\n(a - b)(a^2 + ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 - 7^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 343", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x - 2)(x^2 + 2x + 4)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is negative.\nFactor the equation using the difference of cubes formula.\n(a - b)(a^2 + ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 - 2^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x - 3)(x^2 + 3x + 9)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is negative.\nFactor the equation using the difference of cubes formula.\n(a - b)(a^2 + ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 - 3^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 27", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 2)(x - 2)", "-(x - 2)(-x - 2)", "(-x + 2)(-x - 2)", "-(-x + 2)(x + 2)"], "answer": "(x + 2)(x - 2)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 2^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 2^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 8)(x - 8)", "-(x - 8)(-x - 8)", "(-x + 8)(-x - 8)", "-(-x + 8)(x + 8)"], "answer": "(x + 8)(x - 8)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 8^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 8^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 64", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x - 3)(x^2 + 3x + 9)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is negative.\nFactor the equation using the difference of cubes formula.\n(a - b)(a^2 + ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 - 3^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 27", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 8)(x + 8)", "-(x + 8)(-x + 8)", "(-x - 8)(-x + 8)", "-(-x - 8)(x - 8)"], "answer": "(x - 8)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 8^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 8^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 64", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 2)(x^2 - 2x + 4)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is positive.\nFactor the equation using the sum of cubes formula.\n(a + b)(a^2 - ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 + 2^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 8", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(7x + 5)(7x - 5)", "-(7x - 5)(-7x - 5)", "(-7x + 5)(-7x - 5)", "-(-7x + 5)(7x + 5)"], "answer": "(7x + 5)(7x - 5)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (7x)^2 - 5^2\na \u003d (7x)^2, b \u003d 5^2", "question": "Factor:\n49x^2 - 25", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 5)(x - 5)", "-(x - 5)(-x - 5)", "(-x + 5)(-x - 5)", "-(-x + 5)(x + 5)"], "answer": "(x + 5)(x - 5)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 5^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 5^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 25", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(7x - 1)(7x + 1)", "-(7x + 1)(-7x + 1)", "(-7x - 1)(-7x + 1)", "-(-7x - 1)(7x - 1)"], "answer": "(7x - 1)(7x + 1)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (7x)^2 - 1^2\na \u003d (7x)^2, b \u003d 1^2", "question": "Factor:\n49x^2 - 1", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 7)(x - 7)", "-(x - 7)(-x - 7)", "(-x + 7)(-x - 7)", "-(-x + 7)(x + 7)"], "answer": "(x + 7)(x - 7)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 7^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 7^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 49", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 9)(x - 9)", "-(x - 9)(-x - 9)", "(-x + 9)(-x - 9)", "-(-x + 9)(x + 9)"], "answer": "(x + 9)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 9^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 9^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 81", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x - 5)(x^2 + 5x + 25)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is negative.\nFactor the equation using the difference of cubes formula.\n(a - b)(a^2 + ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 - 5^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 125", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(4x + 9)(4x - 9)", "-(4x - 9)(-4x - 9)", "(-4x + 9)(-4x - 9)", "-(-4x + 9)(4x + 9)"], "answer": "(4x + 9)(4x - 9)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (4x)^2 - 9^2\na \u003d (4x)^2, b \u003d 9^2", "question": "Factor:\n16x^2 - 81", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 7)(x^2 - 7x + 49)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is positive.\nFactor the equation using the sum of cubes formula.\n(a + b)(a^2 - ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 + 7^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 343", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(10x - 4)(10x + 4)", "-(10x + 4)(-10x + 4)", "(-10x - 4)(-10x + 4)", "-(-10x - 4)(10x - 4)"], "answer": "(10x - 4)(10x + 4)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (10x)^2 - 4^2\na \u003d (10x)^2, b \u003d 4^2", "question": "Factor:\n100x^2 - 16", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 6)(x + 6)", "-(x + 6)(-x + 6)", "(-x - 6)(-x + 6)", "-(-x - 6)(x - 6)"], "answer": "(x - 6)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 6^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 6^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 36", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(4x - 7)(4x + 7)", "-(4x + 7)(-4x + 7)", "(-4x - 7)(-4x + 7)", "-(-4x - 7)(4x - 7)"], "answer": "(4x - 7)(4x + 7)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (4x)^2 - 7^2\na \u003d (4x)^2, b \u003d 7^2", "question": "Factor:\n16x^2 - 49", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x - 7)(x^2 + 7x + 49)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is negative.\nFactor the equation using the difference of cubes formula.\n(a - b)(a^2 + ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 - 7^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 343", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 4)(x - 4)", "-(x - 4)(-x - 4)", "(-x + 4)(-x - 4)", "-(-x + 4)(x + 4)"], "answer": "(x + 4)(x - 4)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 4^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 4^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 16", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(10x + 2)(10x - 2)", "-(10x - 2)(-10x - 2)", "(-10x + 2)(-10x - 2)", "-(-10x + 2)(10x + 2)"], "answer": "(10x + 2)(10x - 2)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (10x)^2 - 2^2\na \u003d (10x)^2, b \u003d 2^2", "question": "Factor:\n100x^2 - 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x - 8)(x^2 + 8x + 64)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is negative.\nFactor the equation using the difference of cubes formula.\n(a - b)(a^2 + ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 - 8^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 512", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(7x + 3)(7x - 3)", "-(7x - 3)(-7x - 3)", "(-7x + 3)(-7x - 3)", "-(-7x + 3)(7x + 3)"], "answer": "(7x + 3)(7x - 3)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (7x)^2 - 3^2\na \u003d (7x)^2, b \u003d 3^2", "question": "Factor:\n49x^2 - 9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 6)(x + 6)", "-(x + 6)(-x + 6)", "(-x - 6)(-x + 6)", "-(-x - 6)(x - 6)"], "answer": "(x - 6)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 6^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 6^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 36", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(6x + 6)(6x - 6)", "-(6x - 6)(-6x - 6)", "(-6x + 6)(-6x - 6)", "-(-6x + 6)(6x + 6)"], "answer": "(6x + 6)(6x - 6)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (6x)^2 - 6^2\na \u003d (6x)^2, b \u003d 6^2", "question": "Factor:\n36x^2 - 36", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 9)(x - 9)", "-(x - 9)(-x - 9)", "(-x + 9)(-x - 9)", "-(-x + 9)(x + 9)"], "answer": "(x + 9)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 9^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 9^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 81", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x - 8)(3x + 8)", "-(3x + 8)(-3x + 8)", "(-3x - 8)(-3x + 8)", "-(-3x - 8)(3x - 8)"], "answer": "(3x - 8)(3x + 8)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (3x)^2 - 8^2\na \u003d (3x)^2, b \u003d 8^2", "question": "Factor:\n9x^2 - 64", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 3)(x - 3)", "-(x - 3)(-x - 3)", "(-x + 3)(-x - 3)", "-(-x + 3)(x + 3)"], "answer": "(x + 3)(x - 3)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 3^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 3^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 4)(x + 4)", "-(x + 4)(-x + 4)", "(-x - 4)(-x + 4)", "-(-x - 4)(x - 4)"], "answer": "(x - 4)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 4^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 4^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 16", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 9)(x - 9)", "-(x - 9)(-x - 9)", "(-x + 9)(-x - 9)", "-(-x + 9)(x + 9)"], "answer": "(x + 9)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 9^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 9^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 81", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(4x - 9)(4x + 9)", "-(4x + 9)(-4x + 9)", "(-4x - 9)(-4x + 9)", "-(-4x - 9)(4x - 9)"], "answer": "(4x - 9)(4x + 9)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (4x)^2 - 9^2\na \u003d (4x)^2, b \u003d 9^2", "question": "Factor:\n16x^2 - 81", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 6)(x^2 - 6x + 36)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is positive.\nFactor the equation using the sum of cubes formula.\n(a + b)(a^2 - ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 + 6^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 216", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x - 8)(x^2 + 8x + 64)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is negative.\nFactor the equation using the difference of cubes formula.\n(a - b)(a^2 + ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 - 8^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 512", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(6x + 6)(6x - 6)", "-(6x - 6)(-6x - 6)", "(-6x + 6)(-6x - 6)", "-(-6x + 6)(6x + 6)"], "answer": "(6x + 6)(6x - 6)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (6x)^2 - 6^2\na \u003d (6x)^2, b \u003d 6^2", "question": "Factor:\n36x^2 - 36", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 9)(x - 9)", "-(x - 9)(-x - 9)", "(-x + 9)(-x - 9)", "-(-x + 9)(x + 9)"], "answer": "(x + 9)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 9^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 9^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 81", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 10)(x - 10)", "-(x - 10)(-x - 10)", "(-x + 10)(-x - 10)", "-(-x + 10)(x + 10)"], "answer": "(x + 10)(x - 10)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 10^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 10^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 100", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 10)(x + 10)", "-(x + 10)(-x + 10)", "(-x - 10)(-x + 10)", "-(-x - 10)(x - 10)"], "answer": "(x - 10)(x + 10)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 10^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 10^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 100", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 4)(x - 4)", "-(x - 4)(-x - 4)", "(-x + 4)(-x - 4)", "-(-x + 4)(x + 4)"], "answer": "(x + 4)(x - 4)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 4^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 4^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 16", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(10x - 8)(10x + 8)", "-(10x + 8)(-10x + 8)", "(-10x - 8)(-10x + 8)", "-(-10x - 8)(10x - 8)"], "answer": "(10x - 8)(10x + 8)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (10x)^2 - 8^2\na \u003d (10x)^2, b \u003d 8^2", "question": "Factor:\n100x^2 - 64", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(10x + 9)(10x - 9)", "-(10x - 9)(-10x - 9)", "(-10x + 9)(-10x - 9)", "-(-10x + 9)(10x + 9)"], "answer": "(10x + 9)(10x - 9)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (10x)^2 - 9^2\na \u003d (10x)^2, b \u003d 9^2", "question": "Factor:\n100x^2 - 81", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x - 9)(x^2 + 9x + 81)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is negative.\nFactor the equation using the difference of cubes formula.\n(a - b)(a^2 + ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 - 9^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 729", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 8)(x^2 - 8x + 64)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is positive.\nFactor the equation using the sum of cubes formula.\n(a + b)(a^2 - ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 + 8^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 512", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 5)(2x - 5)", "-(2x - 5)(-2x - 5)", "(-2x + 5)(-2x - 5)", "-(-2x + 5)(2x + 5)"], "answer": "(2x + 5)(2x - 5)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (2x)^2 - 5^2\na \u003d (2x)^2, b \u003d 5^2", "question": "Factor:\n4x^2 - 25", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(7x + 9)(7x - 9)", "-(7x - 9)(-7x - 9)", "(-7x + 9)(-7x - 9)", "-(-7x + 9)(7x + 9)"], "answer": "(7x + 9)(7x - 9)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (7x)^2 - 9^2\na \u003d (7x)^2, b \u003d 9^2", "question": "Factor:\n49x^2 - 81", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 2)(x + 2)", "-(x + 2)(-x + 2)", "(-x - 2)(-x + 2)", "-(-x - 2)(x - 2)"], "answer": "(x - 2)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 2^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 2^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 5)(x - 5)", "-(x - 5)(-x - 5)", "(-x + 5)(-x - 5)", "-(-x + 5)(x + 5)"], "answer": "(x + 5)(x - 5)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 5^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 5^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 25", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(5x - 3)(5x + 3)", "-(5x + 3)(-5x + 3)", "(-5x - 3)(-5x + 3)", "-(-5x - 3)(5x - 3)"], "answer": "(5x - 3)(5x + 3)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (5x)^2 - 3^2\na \u003d (5x)^2, b \u003d 3^2", "question": "Factor:\n25x^2 - 9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 8)(x - 8)", "-(x - 8)(-x - 8)", "(-x + 8)(-x - 8)", "-(-x + 8)(x + 8)"], "answer": "(x + 8)(x - 8)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 8^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 8^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 64", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 2)(x - 2)", "-(x - 2)(-x - 2)", "(-x + 2)(-x - 2)", "-(-x + 2)(x + 2)"], "answer": "(x + 2)(x - 2)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 2^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 2^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 4", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(9x + 8)(9x - 8)", "-(9x - 8)(-9x - 8)", "(-9x + 8)(-9x - 8)", "-(-9x + 8)(9x + 8)"], "answer": "(9x + 8)(9x - 8)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (9x)^2 - 8^2\na \u003d (9x)^2, b \u003d 8^2", "question": "Factor:\n81x^2 - 64", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 2)(x^2 - 2x + 4)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is positive.\nFactor the equation using the sum of cubes formula.\n(a + b)(a^2 - ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 + 2^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x - 8)(x^2 + 8x + 64)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is negative.\nFactor the equation using the difference of cubes formula.\n(a - b)(a^2 + ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 - 8^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 512", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x - 2)(x^2 + 2x + 4)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is negative.\nFactor the equation using the difference of cubes formula.\n(a - b)(a^2 + ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 - 2^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 8", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 3)(x - 3)", "-(x - 3)(-x - 3)", "(-x + 3)(-x - 3)", "-(-x + 3)(x + 3)"], "answer": "(x + 3)(x - 3)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 3^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 3^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 9", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 8)(x + 8)", "-(x + 8)(-x + 8)", "(-x - 8)(-x + 8)", "-(-x - 8)(x - 8)"], "answer": "(x - 8)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 8^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 8^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 64", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 9)(x - 9)", "-(x - 9)(-x - 9)", "(-x + 9)(-x - 9)", "-(-x + 9)(x + 9)"], "answer": "(x + 9)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 9^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 9^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 81", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 4)(x - 4)", "-(x - 4)(-x - 4)", "(-x + 4)(-x - 4)", "-(-x + 4)(x + 4)"], "answer": "(x + 4)(x - 4)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 4^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 4^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 16", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x - 6)(x^2 + 6x + 36)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is negative.\nFactor the equation using the difference of cubes formula.\n(a - b)(a^2 + ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 - 6^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 216", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 7)(x^2 - 7x + 49)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is positive.\nFactor the equation using the sum of cubes formula.\n(a + b)(a^2 - ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 + 7^3", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 343", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x + 4)(x - 4)", "-(x - 4)(-x - 4)", "(-x + 4)(-x - 4)", "-(-x + 4)(x + 4)"], "answer": "(x + 4)(x - 4)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 4^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 4^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 16", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(7x - 6)(7x + 6)", "-(7x + 6)(-7x + 6)", "(-7x - 6)(-7x + 6)", "-(-7x - 6)(7x - 6)"], "answer": "(7x - 6)(7x + 6)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (7x)^2 - 6^2\na \u003d (7x)^2, b \u003d 6^2", "question": "Factor:\n49x^2 - 36", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(x - 6)(x + 6)", "-(x + 6)(-x + 6)", "(-x - 6)(-x + 6)", "-(-x - 6)(x - 6)"], "answer": "(x - 6)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 6^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 6^2", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 36", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(6x + 9)(6x - 9)", "-(6x - 9)(-6x - 9)", "(-6x + 9)(-6x - 9)", "-(-6x + 9)(6x + 9)"], "answer": "(6x + 9)(6x - 9)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (6x)^2 - 9^2\na \u003d (6x)^2, b \u003d 9^2", "question": "Factor:\n36x^2 - 81", "type": "text"}
]}